Hey.
Hey, boss. I got your text.
What's up?
I got a call
from the FBI.
What do they want?
It's about the investigation
of Craig O'Laughlin's death.
Oh.
It was an agent
named Wexler.
He said he'd been
trying to reach you.
Yeah, he left some messages.
I haven't called him back.
What did he say?
The investigation's over.
They've filed the report.
He just wanted you to know that
he was returning your necklace.
My what?
The necklace
O'Laughlin gave you.
It was in evidence,
but they're done with it.
He sent it over.
I don't..
Look, I don't want it.
You take it.
If you don't want it,
you can sell it
or take it
to the evidence room
and they can auction it off.
Here, it's for you.
[gunshots]
Hey, boss..
Caught one. Shooting victim
out in El Oro State Forest.
You two take it.
- Grace? Are you okay?
- Fine, yeah.
- You want me to take it away?
- No, it's okay.
El Oro State Forest, that's
East of Lake Tahoe, right?
Yeah.
[instrumental music]
You get lost?
Briefly.
Beautiful out here, though they
could use a little more signage.
Victim's name's
Gabriel Porchetto Junior.
Father's a big mob boss.
Runs narcotics and illegal
gambling in the Northeast.
They live in the city.
This is a vacation house.
"Porchetto"
that's Argentinian, I believe.
How can you tell?
I used to read
a lot of phone books.
As I recall, Buenos Aires
had many Porchettos.
You used to read phone books.
Yes, it's an excellent mnemonic
exercise. You should try it.
[Cho]
'Porchetto and his younger
brother were throwing a party.'
'Had a half-dozen friends here.'
Brought in hookers
for entertainment.
Good, wholesome fun.
There's a security fence
around the entire compound.
About a hundred yards
that way
there's a blanket
thrown over the barbed wire
and footprints inside and out.
Looks like the point of entry.
Hmm.
And here we are.
Ugh.
Which one's
the younger brother?
Sergio.
Yeah?
So you're Sergio,
and, uh...who are you?
Curtis Nett.
I work for the family.
The enforcer.
Ten years.
Just tell us what happened.
We were inside
the house, partying.
Gabe came out to the hot tub
with one of the girls.
There's a shot.
Curtis and I run out and..
Gabe's...you know.
Girl's freaking out.
I run to the fence.
I see a guy just climbed over.
I throw a shot at him.
He throws a shot at me.
No one hit anything.
He takes off running.
You get a look at him?
White guy, jacket,
baseball cap.
'You gave your gun
to the sheriff, right?'
That's right.
We need all the other guns
even the ones hidden.
Look at this mess. You want to
talk some crap weapons charges?
We won't necessarily
press charges
but I need every gun
for a ballistics check.
I'll tell the guys.
You do that, Serge.
So what's the deal?
You work for the family,
but you have no respect for him.
Is that a question?
I don't know. Was it?
Where's the girl?
That's a question.
[sighs]
Her name is Janpen.
She's Chinese.
Doesn't speak English.
Okay. Hi.
My name is Patrick.
[speaks Chinese]
We're gonna need
a translator.
What is that hideous thing
on her shoulder?
[singsongy]
She speaks English.
She's just a little
bit shy, right?
I don't speak English.
Guys don't talk to me.
It's better that way.
So what did you see
when Mr. Porchetto was shot?
Nothing. There's a loud bang
scares the crap out of me, and..
...the guy's dead. I mean,
I freaked out. That's it.
What'd the shooter
look like?
Didn't see him.
You're a good liar.
Good, not great.
She saw him close up.
I know who these guys are,
I'm not getting involved.
Maybe you shot him.
Yeah, I hid the gun
in my pants.
I'm taking you in.
We'll talk at the office.
I don't have to go with you.
I could arrest you
for prostitution..
...is that how
you want to do it?
Well, can I put
some clothes on first?
Sure.
Interesting girl.
So what's
your take on this?
Well, the fresh air,
my first mob hit..
I'm thrilled.
[shuts glove compartment]
What?
The GPS says turn right,
but I think it's confused.
Morning. You lost?
We're fine, thanks.
[gunshots]
Ah!
Hang on!
[theme music]
[panting]
Hey. You okay?
Hey! Hey!
Hey! Stop.
Stop. I will shoot you.
Nice driving.
Don't waste your time.
There's no signal.
Um..
there was some noise over there,
like some kind of animal.
Freaked me out.
Unlock me, okay?
We can't stay here, and we
can't go back up to the road.
There's too much chance
of running into that guy.
We follow the stream
East a ways
we'll probably run
into State Route four.
We can catch
a cell signal there.
I'm not going anywhere.
It's not a choice.
Can't make me.
We need help.
I'm trying to protect you.
Yeah, so I can testify
against the mob.
Forget it.
Okay.
- I'll go by myself.
- Cool. Unlock me.
I need to know where to find you
when we come back for you.
Hey, you can't do that.
Watch out
for rattlesnakes.
'They're all over
through these woods.'
Okay, wait!
[male #1]
'I've spoken
with the forestry service.'
They're beginning
a coordinated search
with the sheriff's office.
It's likely the GPS
gave Van Pelt bad directions.
They've had people
lost this way.
They don't think
she's gonna be hard to find.
Get some of our people looking.
More boots on the ground.
They're not taking
this seriously.
How big is the area
they're searching?
One hundred and forty
square miles.
It sounds pretty serious.
If you were there,
we'd look for you.
I hope not.
If I'm lost, I want
a search-and-rescue team
that knows the landscape
and can cover ground fast.
Now I will make sure
every resource is devoted
to finding Van Pelt. Okay?
Meantime, let's do our jobs.
Boss, we need to be--
He's right.
We don't know the terrain.
We'll just get in the way.
Let's focus on what we cando.
What do you got?
Ballistics came in.
Junior was shot with a .380.
One casing found
at the crime scene
another, 10 yards
outside the fence.
That must've been the shot
the killer fired at Nett
when he was running away.
- Any luck on the gun trace?
- No. Nothing.
This feels like a hit to me,
like a pro at work.
He had to have driven there.
Let's check the gas stations
and the convenience stores
on the road to the cabin.
Maybe he stopped off somewhere.
Do we have anything
on the witness Janpen?
No arrests. The other hookers
didn't have anything to say.
I'm trying to find the pimp
that arranged the party.
Take a hard look at
the wise guys that were there.
If someone would know how
to hire a hit man, it's them.
Van Pelt will be
back here in 20 minutes
and we're all gonna
feel stupid for worrying.
File on Porchetto Senior's
quite an interesting read.
Murder, robbery, thuggery,
all sorts of skullduggery.
The organized crime unit's been
after Porchetto for a while.
There's nothing more
you can do.
About what?
Van Pelt. That's what
you're fretting about.
Van Pelt is missing
because of the murder
ergo, we focus on
catching the murderer
chances are
we'll find Van Pelt..
unless someone else
finds her first, but right now?
Let's go. Porchettos.
Agent Lisbon. Mr. Jane.
Andrew Kellogg.
I'm the Porchettos' attorney.
This is Iris Porchetto,
Gabe's stepmother.
Where is Mr. Porchetto?
On his way.
He's not feeling well.
We'll have to
keep this brief.
We'll have to be thorough
but I'll keep
your concerns in mind.
Let's play cards up, agent.
The police have unjustly hounded
the Porchettos for years.
I will not stand
for that sort of thing.
'These the cops?'
[Lisbon]
We're with the CBI,
Mr. Porchetto.
This is who they send
to find my boy's killer?
A girl and a guy in a vest.
This is really a waste
of my time.
- I want a drink.
- No.
Gabe is dead.
I can have a drink.
Not with your meds.
It's got bad interaction.
Uh, excuse me.
Where is the cancer?
What's your name?
Jane. Patrick Jane.
Liver? Kidney? Spleen?
Kidney.
Oh. How long
did they give you?
"How long"? I'm a dead man.
That's how long.
Having trouble sleeping,
I expect.
Yes. Why?
Well, I can tell you
how to get to sleep
if you tell us
who you think killed your son.
Who says I know?
You said you were
wasting your time with us
so I assumed you already knew
who was responsible.
Do you, Mr. Porchetto?
- Don't say anything.
- Honey, listen to Andrew.
This one can't wait
to put me in the ground.
That's not true.
Maybe just a little true?
You want me
to do your job? Fine.
It was the Mexicans.
What Mexicans?
Julio Iglesias.
Who do you think?
The Zetas.
- The Mexican drug cartel?
- Yeah.
Why would they want
to kill your son?
I'm not saying any more.
About that sleeping trick..
Oh, yes.
When you breathe in, count one.
When you breathe out, count two.
In one, out two. Very simple.
Think of nothing else, except
your breath and those numbers.
And that will make me sleep?
Like a big, murderous baby.
Ciao.
Organized crime unit says
Junior wanted the Porchettos
to sell meth in the Northeast.
The Zetas control the drug trade
in that territory.
If junior did make a move,
they could've killed him.
Call Bernie Westeroff
in narcotics.
See if he has a line on any
Zeta foot soldiers in the area.
You're gonna get
a Mexican drug dealer to talk?
- I'll think of something.
- Ohh.
Wayne.
Sarah.
Yeah, I was looking for you.
Lunch.
Oh. Damn. I forgot.
[sighs]
No, look, I'm sorry.
Grace is missing.
Oh, my lord.
What's happened?
We-we don't know. Look,
she was in a state park and..
anyway, I have to work.
I'm sorry.
Of course. You work.
We'll just do it another time.
Yeah. Just call me
later, okay?
And I'm sure it's fine.
She's fine.
Thanks.
Um..
It's really hard
to walk like this.
Should have thought of that
before you ran.
[rustle]
Stay here.
[wings flapping]
'Hey, Grace.'
[pants]
- Who are you?
- Come on, Grace.
Craig's dead. I killed him.
Yeah. Yeah, you did that.
Are you a ghost?
What do you think?
If you're not a ghost,
what are you?
Grace, look, you've been
in a car accident.
You're dehydrated,
pumped on adrenaline.
Maybe I'm just
something you're seeing.
The question is, why now?
Why do you need
to see me, Grace?
[Janpen]
'Hey!'
What's going on?
Nothing. Let's keep walking.
Hey, Lisbon.
What'd you get
for me, Bernie?
You wanted a Zeta,
I got you one. Luis Osorio.
A lieutenant, connected,
should know stuff.
- I owe you one. Thanks.
- Yeah, maybe not.
The charge I got Osorio on
is bogus, and he knows it
so he'll keep his mouth shut.
His lawyer gets here, he walks.
I like my chances.
Hi, Mr. Osorio.
Uh, Patrick Jane.
'Sorry we've kept you so long.'
Promise we won't
keep you much longer.
[sighs]
You play cards?
'Want to play a little game?'
It's find the queen. Alright?
There she is there.
All you have to do is find her.
You follow the queen, you keep
an eye on where she goes
and then you bet.
There. Not here. There she is.
[cards clack]
Where is she?
I don't give a damn
where she is.
[Patrick]
Hmm.
What do you think I am?
A child?
Excuse me. I was just trying
to kill a little time.
[clacking]
- Where is she?
- 'She's on the right.'
- Hmm. How you do that?
- The hype.
You pick up two cards
between your fingers like so
but when you throw down
it appears that you throw
the bottom card
when in fact,
you throw the top card..
Like that. See how that looked
like it was the bottom card?
Huh. Nice.
You hold it like that, you just
drop it down there like that.
'It's very easy.
Lot of practice.'
It's fun to watch, when you
know what's happening, isn't it?
Kind of relaxing. Soothing.
[cards clacking]
Tell me something.
You think the Zetas
killed Gabriel Porchetto?
Nah. Zetas didn't have
any reason to kill him.
Not yet, anyhow.
Man was all talk.
Good to know.
Alright, you try.
'Go ahead.'
[rustle]
Look at you.
You're a natural.
Look at the way
you hold those cards.
'And you drop the first one
down, just like that.'
Two hands, let it flop.
That's a beginning,
that's a start. Baby steps.
Who do you think
killed Porchetto?
Well, people say, uh..
...he got into a fight
with a biker..
biker named Wood. Ha.
Almost have it. Almost.
You can swindle people
before you behead them
or whatever it is
you do to them.
I never beheaded nobody.
Slit a few throats maybe.
Okay. Zero beheadings.
Hmm.
[Cho]
'Ran the biker named Wood.'
There's an incident report
on a bar fight Junior had
with a gang member named
Elwood Spiller two weeks ago.
No arrest. Spiller refused
to press charges.
- Find out what it was about.
- Boss, check this out.
Nothing from the gas stations
in the area
but I found some video cameras
near the crime scene
some professor studying
animal migration patterns.
One of them caught a white male
driving near the cabin
right after the shooting.
Did they get the plate?
'No, but we were able
to enhance the image.'
Asked the FBI to run it
through facial recognition
and this one
seemed like the best shot.
Raynor Marquette. He's from L.A.
He's got a long sheet.
FBI thinks
he runs guns into Tijuana
and that
he's a killer for hire.
See if you can find out
anything else
and send that picture
to the county sheriff's office.
Okay. Hey.
You, uh, hear anything?
They've covered 40%
of the search area. Nothing yet.
[water trickling]
So where are you from?
Barstow.
A cousin of my mom's
raised me.
Meth head. Not so great
with the mother thing.
She got me started
in this massage parlor.
I was, like, 11, maybe.
I wasn't the youngest.
Anyways,
a couple years after
this Guatemalan arms dealer
bought me..
...and I was, like, his pet.
And that was
kind of weird.
And then he got k..
Ow!
- Are you okay?
- No!
Bitch, take these off.
Like I'm gonna run. Where?
I have no idea where we are
or how to get to where
you say we're going.
'Last thing I'm gonna do
is take off.'
Alright.
Thank you.
It'll be dark soon.
We need to find a place
to spend the night.
Um..
Shouldn't there be people out
looking for us? Where arethey?
I don't know. Come on.
Come on.
[whirring]
Elwood Spiller.
Kimball Cho, CBI.
I want to talk
about Junior Porchetto.
Did you and he
have a fight on the 17th?
No, we did not.
Well, according to
the incident report
you got into an argument
with Junior
and he had three of his guys
beat you to a pulp.
- Nope.
- Well, how'd all this happen?
- A boating accident.
- Now junior did this to you.
Now you must have
a major grudge.
We can talk about it here,
or I'll take you in
you can sit in a cell
and talk about it tomorrow.
Old man Porchetto
is on a hunt.
Anybody he thinks had anything
to do with hitting Junior
is gonna get clipped.
So you can take me
wherever you'd like.
All I'm saying
is Junior Porchetto
was one hell of a guy
and he always
treated me good.
[sighs]
You do know
his old man is sick, right?
When he dies, come back.
I might say
something different.
Interesting.
He said, come back
after the father's dead.
That's right.
That's interesting.
We know killing Junior
was a major play.
Whoever did it
took a big risk.
Must've expected a big payoff.
Who's that?
Hard to say. According to
the organized crime unit
the main person who benefits
from Junior's death
- is old man Porchetto himself.
- Why?
Well, if they moved in
after Zeta territory
the way that Junior wanted,
they would've started a war.
Could've ended
the Porchetto organization.
Junior was getting in
way over his head.
[cell phone rings]
It's the sheriff's office.
Lisbon.
Okay, thank you.
They're suspending the search
for the night.
They're gonna start again
in the morning.
They're doing something wrong.
They should've
found her by now.
They're doing something wrong.
Um, either of you play squash?
[Lisbon]
'What?'
You know, squash.
- No.
I need a squash ball.
It's about that big
little, black thing.
Doesn't bounce very well.
I know what you want to ask.
Don't be embarrassed.
I am not talking to you.
You are just a figment
of my imagination.
Please yourself.
Did you love me?
Of course I loved you.
Then why did you
try to kill me?
I had to make a choice
between you and Red John.
We all have to make
hard choices, Grace
Doesn't make me evil.
[scoffs]
Kind of does.
Grace
I was just too stupid
to see it.
- Oh, no, you saw it.
- No, I didn't.
Not all of it, but you knew
there was something..
something a little dangerous
under the nice guy stuff.
You kind of liked it.
You can't open your eyes
a little bit.
Gotta open 'em all the way
if you wanna see the truth.
What are you talking about?
Why are you doing this
to me?
How should I know?
I'm just a figment
of your imagination.
Damn it.
[whispers]
Hey.
Did you find
your squash ball?
Oh, yes, I did,
as a matter of fact. Thank you.
Um, I'm headed over
to the Porchettos.
Why?
It probably won't work,
but if it does
you're gonna have to move fast,
so stay on your toes.
Boss. They're looking
in the wrong place.
- What do you mean?
- The searchers messed up.
That's why they haven't
found anything.
They started the search
at the last cell phone tower
that Van Pelt's phone
made contact with.
They figured she was within
a 15-mile radius of this point.
- That makes sense.
- But they're wrong. I checked.
The next tower, here, was down
for maintenance yesterday.
If her phone tried to make
contact with thistower
there'd be no record.
They should be looking
10 miles further.
I'm going out there.
You go.
I'll deal with Wainwright.
[cell phone rings]
Hey, sir.
Wayne, hi.
Um, I know you're busy.
I was just wondering
how things are.
We still haven't found her
yet. I'm heading out there.
Um, well, I just want you to
know I was thinking about you
and praying for Grace,
and..
I just know that this is
gonna turn out alright.
Thanks.
Listen, I have to go.
The, uh, elevator's here.
I'll call you later, yeah?
Janpen?!
Don't blame yourself.
I fell asleep.
Yeah. You were tired.
She gets lost,
she could die.
Why did I think
I could stay awake?
Everything isn't your fault.
This is my fault.
- I wasn't your fault.
- Yes, you were.
You were with me when you killed
those cops and you shot Lisbon.
I should have stopped you.
You did.
You killed me.
I was too late.
I should have seen it sooner.
I should have done something.
How? You were in love with me.
Don't you remember?
There she is.
- Where'd you go?
- I had to pee.
Who were you talking to?
- Nobody.
- Great.
Lost in the woods
with a crazy cop.
Hey, I got it worse.
I'm lost in the woods
with a grumpy hooker. Let's go.
The silent intimidation act
is quite effective.
I'll admit, I'm intimidated.
Then he forced himself in here,
and won't leave.
- You have to do something--
- Iris. You need to relax.
Tension causes wrinkles.
Mr. Jane,
what are you doing here?
- I need to speak to Porchetto.
- You can't talk to him.
Yes, I can.
Do you see what I mean?
This is...
If you don't leave,
I'll protest to your superiors.
You can't harass my client
like this.
How long have you two been
carrying on this affair?
What do you mean?
Your protectiveness of Iris
is more than legal
and she keeps touching your
elbow. Hard to misinterpret.
I'm pretty sure
Curtis here already knows.
Yes, he looks dense,
but he's as sharp as a tack.
Doesn't miss a beat,
do you, Curtis?
This is...
completely irrelevant.
Are you worried
that Porchetto's gonna find out
or does it add
a more excitement?
- Did you just threaten us?
- Let's take a breath here.
[Porchetto]
'What's going on?'
You.
Well, good morning.
That trick, one two, one two...
damned if it doesn't work.
- Fell asleep in no time.
- Glad to hear it.
What do you want?
Do you think we could
talk someplace else?
It's kind of
a private matter.
So what is it?
Well, colleague of mine
is missing.
I think it's connected
to your son's murder.
You're still looking
for the murderer, right?
Maybe.
Sure you are.
You want to kill him.
I get it, believe me.
But have you found him?
'Cause I'd like to talk to him
Then you can have him back,
Do whatever you want with him.
I don't know
anything about it.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, I'm sure.
Crap.
You were my last hope.
Okay. What do I do now?
I could use a drink. Um...
You don't have any vodka,
do you?
I can't have booze around.
My meds.
Surely, you got a stash.
A man like you
would have a stash.
I only want a nip, just..
Maybe two.
Really craving that
warm, comforting feeling
of alcohol hitting
the back of your throat.
You know.
It just levels me.
Uh, don't tell my wife.
Mm. Love that sound.
You're a saint.
Thank you.
[sniffs and sighs]
Mmm.
[sighs]
Yep, that's it.
Just levels me.
It's like an angel
crying on your tongue.
[sighs]
That's good.
You?
Doctors say it messes me up.
Oh, them. Doctors.
Always with the rules.
I mean, as if they know
anything for sure.
One.
[pours vodka]
Ah.
[exhales deeply]
So Mike has a...
pool cue, and, uh...
Cheers.
[glasses clink]
Cheers. And sammy's
right behind me..
and, uh..
and I have a shovel.
He says...
[grunts]
[glass clinks]
Man down! Man down in here!
What the hell happened?
He just fell off.
I don't know.
Does he have a pulse?
Check.
I don't feel anything.
- Let me check.
- Oh, my God.
Is he breathing? I can't
tell if he's breathing.
- I'm not getting a pulse.
- I don't think he's breathing.
Is this it? Is this happening?
Oh, my God.
- Someone call an ambulance!
- I'll call right now.
What should we do?
We should do something.
I'll get the guys.
We can't just leave him here.
It's so undignified.
Do you have somewhere
you can lay him down?
- 'In the front room.'
- Front room it is, then.
- Guys. Come on, come on!
- I need a hand here.
Porchetto's dead?
Oh, more like drunk.
Are you drunk?
A little.
Let's not get distracted.
[whispers]
I think someone is
staging a coup
inside the Porchetto family
a takeover
when the old man dies.
- That's who killed Junior.
- Why?
Because Junior wanted
to go to war with the zetas--
would have destroyed
the family
before the plotter
could take over.
So you're trying to get
the plotter to reveal himself
by pretending
that Porchetto's dead?
Oh, you're very good,
grasshopper.
Won't the doctors
figure out he's not dead?
They're figuring it out now.
so we have to work fast.
But Van Pelt is missing.
- Excuse me, doctor?
- Yes.
My name's Patrick Jane.
I'm with the CBI.
Do you take bribe money
from big pharma?
What?
That's an offensive suggestion.
Why would you say that?
Well, a lot of doctors...
what's he saying?
I mean, obviously,
in any profession
people fall short
of the ethical mark.
What's that doctor
saying to the cop?
Mm, free trips
to the Bahamas...
Think it's about dad?
Well, thanks for chatting.
What was that doctor saying?
Well, he should probably
tell you himself.
It's not really my place.
Mr. Jane, people are suffering.
Tell us what you know.
We're very sorry
for your loss.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. He's gone.
Son of a bitch.
Can't help but feel
a little responsible here.
- What'd you do to him?
- Serge.
You were the last one
with him.
If I find out
you did anything to him
I swear you're gonna die.
You hear me?
It's not a threat.
It's a promise.
Shut... up.
Alright?
You can't say that to me.
You work for me.
I'm in charge now.
No, you're not.
I am.
I talked to the crews,
all of them. They're with me.
And we're gonna do this
smooth and smart
and we're not gonna
go around threatening cops
in public places.
Got it?
- But you have--
- No.
No, he's right. Wait.
- We will talk at the house.
- You're in charge now?
This is none of your business.
You need to speak
with us alone.
[chuckles]
Right.
You really do.
Wait here.
So?
- What the hell?
- It's an old trick.
Small ball under the arm
stops the blood flowing.
No pulse.
He's alive. That's great.
Not for you.
You hired Raynor Marquette
to kill Junior
because he was getting
in your way, didn't you?
Good luck proving that.
I don't have to prove it
in court. I'll just tell him.
Don't do that.
'I will if I have to.'
'I think Marquette's
put one of my people in danger.'
You're gonna
help us find him...
or I will take you in there
and sign your death warrant.
I think she means it.
We got Marquette's cell phone.
We were able to track it
to state route 4
14 miles east
of Porchetto's cabin.
He must be somewhere nearby.
Yeah, it's pretty close
to here.
I can get some rangers
to meet me there. Thanks.
So do you ever think
about getting out of
you know, sex work?
What kind of car you got?
Piece of crap, I bet.
I drive a Lexus,
fully loaded.
Oh, excuse me.
[chuckles]
There's more to life
than that.
[crack]
Get down.
Stay here.
Don't make a sound.
[gunshots]
Grace Behind you.
[grunting]
Stop.
- Get... off!
- Just... relax.
So I guess we can
call it even now, huh?
Bye, Grace
Look after yourself.
[Rigsby]
'Grace!
Where are you?!'
Over here!
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
[door closes]
This is your chance to do
something for yourself, Janpen.
Marquette's still in the
hospital. You talk first
the D.A. Will take first-degree
murder off the table.
No death penalty.
You want that?
Marquette and I are a team.
Part of the job is
getting closer to the target.
'That's what I do.'
Nett had planted the gun.
[Cho]
'Nett grabbed the gun
when he came out.'
He took it to the fence.
Raynor was waiting.
'We had to make it look like the
shooter came from the outside.'
'That was nett's thing.'
He was terrified
old man Porchetto
would find out
he was behind it.
When I was sleeping, you found
a cell signal, didn't you?
That's how Marquette found us.
You called him.
Just wanted to get out
of there.
- By killing me.
- Oh.
Well, it wasn't personal.
Come on.
I kind of like you. You know,
you're hardcore.
I respect that.
Let's go.
Hey.
How are you feeling?
Better. Okay.
Come here.
[sighs]
[Sarah]
'Hi.'
Oh, hey.
I heard you got back
alright.
Yep. Safe and sound.
Congratulations.
It's just such great news.
I'll see you tomorrow,
Wayne.
Yeah, see you tomorrow.
Excuse me.
You want to get
something to eat?
Yeah. Absolutely.
I'm sorry
if that was uncomfortable.
It didn't mean anything.
Really. Nothing at all.
No, it's okay.
Wayne, I understand.
So... how have you been?
Good. Fine.
I'm pregnant.
Jane?
Mm-hmm.
I'm sorry to ask this,
but..
do you ever talk
to your wife?
Yes, sometimes.
Do you ever see her?
No, never.
If you did see her..
...would you think
you were crazy?
Ah.
Craig came to see you,
didn't he?
Yeah.
What did he want?
I don't know.
This will sound
really weird, but..
...he kind of saved my life.
Figuratively speaking,
I hope.
Yes. I mean, he wasn't...
really there, but..
You can't decide what to do
with the necklace
because it reminds you
of your past.
You can try to forget it..
...or you can learn
to live with it.
Yeah.
Hmm.
Well?
Well what?
What do you think I should do?
Keep it or get rid of it?
Well, I think
that's your call, Grace.
Don't you?
Goodnight.
Goodnight, Jane.
[clink]